let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answer: "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options: [
            "A. Hyper Type Multi Language",
            "B. Hyper Text Multiple Language",
            "C. Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "D. Home Text Multi Language"

        ]
    }, 
     {
        numb: 2,
        question: "The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is-",
        answer: "D. HTML, Head, Title, Body",
        options: [
            "A. Head, Title, HTML, Body",
            "B. HTML, Body, Head, Title",
            "C. HTML, Title, Body, Head",
            "D. HTML, Head, Title, Body"

        ]
    }, 
     {
        numb: 3,
        question: "The <hr> tag in HTML is used for-",
        answer: "D. horizontal ruler",
        options: [
            "A. new line",
            "B. vertical ruler",
            "C. new paragraph",
            "D. horizontal ruler"

        ]
    }, 
{
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is used to read an HTML page and render it?",
    answer: "C. Web browser",
    options: [
        "A. Web server",
        "B. Web network",
        "C. Web browser",
        "D. Web matrix"
    ]
}, 
 {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which element is used for or styling HTML5 layout?",
    answer: "A. CSS",

    options: [
        "A. CSS",
        "B. jQuery",
        "C. JavaScript",
        "D. PHP"

    ]
},
{
    numb: 6,
    question: "The full form of CSS is:",
    answer: "B. Cascading Style Sheets",

    options: [
        "A. Coloured Special Sheets",
        "B. Cascading Style Sheets",
        "C. Color and Style Sheets",
        "D. None of the above",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "How can we change the background color of an element?",
    answer: "A. background-color",

    options: [
        "A. background-color",
        "B. color",
        "C. Both A and B",
        "D. None of the above",
        ]
},
{
    numb: 8,
    question: "The CSS property used to specify the transperancy of an element is?",
    answer: "C. opacity",

    options: [
        "A. visibility",
        "B. filter",
        "C. opacity",
        "D. None of the above",
    ]

},
{
    numb: 9,
    question: "How can we specify the spacing between each letter in a text in CSS?",
    answer: "D. letter-spacing",
    
    options: [
        "A. alpha-spacing",
        "B. character-spacing",
        "C.None of the above",
        "D. letter-spacing",
    ]
},
{
    numb: 10,
    question: "We can make rounded borders around elements using which CSS element?",
    answer: "C. border-radius",
    
    options: [
        "A. border-collapse",
        "B. border-round",
        "C. border-radius",
        "D. none of the above",
    ]
},
]; 